* * * *
    
* Links:

This site uses cookies to deliver services to its users. Please take a look at our [Privacy Notice](#) for more information. By clicking AGREE or using the search function you state that you agree to these terms.

AGREE

Privacy Notice
==============

Cookie Policy

**About this Cookie Policy**

This Cookie Policy is provided as an addition to this site's Privacy Notice and exists to explain what cookies are and how they are used on this site. Cookies are tiny text files that are stored within your web broswer or hard drive when you visit a website or web applicaiton. These cookies allow servers to deliver content tailored to individual users or understand user behavior.

**Types of Cookies we use**

This site employs two first-party cookies (served from us and by us that are essential for the site to operate) and two third-party cookies that deliver external services.

**First-Party Cookies**

We use a server-generated session cookie to remember you when you are logged in to the site. This is essential to making sure that your profile details are those that are updated when you log in to make changes. This also lets us know who is logging into the site and when.

This site also uses a cookie that is created by your browser to remember when you agree to the cookie notice popup. This cookie stores nothing but the word "true" if you have agreed to the terms and is deleted when you close your browser. This cookie's only function is to prevent the cookie notice from popping up every time you refresh the site's homepage.

**Third-Party Cookies**

This site uses Google Analytics to understand usage trends and server performance. We do not store variables which are personally-identifiable in Google Analytics like browser ids or IP addresses. Google's privacy policy can be found [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy). If you would prefer have your browser stop supplying information to Google Analytics, Google provides a [browser extension](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) to allow you to do so.

This site also uses cookies supplied by Twitter when the Twitter sidebar script is loaded on the homepage. Their cookie policy is available [here](https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/twitter-cookies). Third-party cookies from Twitter are only loaded on this site's homepage and only when you agree to the terms or click the Twitter logo in the navigation bar.

**How to Disable Cookies Altogether**

Information on how to disable cookies in your browser can be found [here](https://www.aboutcookies.org/how-to-delete-cookies/). Please keep in mind that disabling cookies will prevent the essential functions of most interactive websites and web applications, this site included.

* * *

Privacy Notice

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for (womenalsoknowstuff.com). This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:

1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via completing your profile or from direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. However, as you are voluntarily providing your information to a publicly searchable database, anyone using the site will be able to access your information in the directory. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization. However, anything you enter into your directory profile is publicly searchable and available to anyone using the site. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about changes to this privacy policy. Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by logging into your account/profile or by contacting us via email.

* See what data we have about you, if any. If you have not created a profile and entered in your information voluntarily, you will not be listed in the searchable directory.
* Change/correct any data.
* Have us delete any data we have about you. You can delete information yourself by logging into your account and adjusting your profile as desired. Or you may email us at contact@womenalsoknowstuff.com and request that an administrator delete your entire profile from the system. Once this happens, your name and information will no longer appear on the site or be searchable publicly.
* Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Security**

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect information (provided by you), such as professional information or account passwords, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. We do not have access to your account password, as this information is encrypted and not available to any other site users or administrators. If you forget your password, you may request a password reset. If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice, or need to contact us, we can be reached at .

Close

Terms of Use
============

Terms and Conditions

**Last updated: August 04, 2019**

Please read these Terms and Conditions ("Terms", "Terms and Conditions") carefully before using the http://womenalsoknowstuff.com website (the "Service") operated by Women Also Know Stuff ("us", "we", or "our"). Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned upon your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms. These Terms apply to all visitors, users and others who wish to access or use the Service. By accessing or using the Service you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you disagree with any part of the terms then you do not have permission to access the Service.

**Content**

Our Service allows you to post, link, store, share and otherwise make available certain information, text, graphics, videos, or other material ("Content"). You are responsible for the Content that you post on or through the Service, including its legality, reliability, and appropriateness. By posting Content on or through the Service, You represent and warrant that: (i) the Content is yours (you own it) and/or you have the right to use it and the right to grant us the rights and license as provided in these Terms, and (ii) that the posting of your Content on or through the Service does not violate the privacy rights, publicity rights, copyrights, contract rights or any other rights of any person or entity. We reserve the right to terminate the account of anyone found to be infringing on a copyright. You retain any and all of your rights to any Content you submit, post or display on or through the Service and you are responsible for protecting those rights. We take no responsibility and assume no liability for Content you or any third party posts on or through the Service. However, by posting Content using the Service you grant us the right and license to use, modify, publicly perform, publicly display, reproduce, and distribute such Content on and through the Service. You agree that this license includes the right for us to make your Content available to other users of the Service, who may also use your Content subject to these Terms. Women Also Know Stuff has the right but not the obligation to monitor and edit all Content provided by users. In addition, Content found on or through this Service are the property of Women Also Know Stuff or used with permission. You may not distribute, modify, transmit, reuse, download, repost, copy, or use said Content, whether in whole or in part, for commercial purposes or for personal gain, without express advance written permission from us.

**Accounts**

When you create an account with us, you guarantee that you are above the age of 18, are a woman in the academic field of Political Science, and that the information you provide us is accurate, complete, and current at all times. Inaccurate, incomplete, or obsolete information may result in the immediate termination of your account on the Service. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password, including but not limited to the restriction of access to your computer and/or account. You agree to accept responsibility for any and all activities or actions that occur under your account and/or password, whether your password is with our Service or a third-party service. You must notify us immediately upon becoming aware of any breach of security or unauthorized use of your account.

**Intellectual Property**

The Service and its original content (excluding Content provided by users), features and functionality are and will remain the exclusive property of Women Also Know Stuff and its licensors. The Service is protected by copyright, trademark, and other laws of both the United States and foreign countries. Our trademarks and trade dress may not be used in connection with any product or service without the prior written consent of Women Also Know Stuff. Links To Other Web Sites Our Service may contain links to third party web sites or services that are not owned or controlled by Women Also Know Stuff Women Also Know Stuff has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party web sites or services. We do not warrant the offerings of any of these entities/individuals or their websites. You acknowledge and agree that Women Also Know Stuff shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or through any such third party web sites or services. We strongly advise you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policies of any third party web sites or services that you visit.

**Termination**

We may terminate or suspend your account and bar access to the Service immediately, without prior notice or liability, under our sole discretion, for any reason whatsoever and without limitation, including but not limited to a breach of the Terms. If you wish to terminate your account, you may simply discontinue using the Service, or notify us that you wish to delete your account. All provisions of the Terms which by their nature should survive termination shall survive termination, including, without limitation, ownership provisions, warranty disclaimers, indemnity and limitations of liability.

**Indemnification**

You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Women Also Know Stuff and its licensee and licensors, and their employees, contractors, agents, officers and directors, from and against any and all claims, damages, obligations, losses, liabilities, costs or debt, and expenses (including but not limited to attorney's fees), resulting from or arising out of a) your use and access of the Service, by you or any person using your account and password; b) a breach of these Terms, or c) Content posted on the Service.

**Limitation Of Liability**

In no event shall Women Also Know Stuff, nor its directors, employees, partners, agents, suppliers, or affiliates, be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, consequential or punitive damages, including without limitation, loss of profits, data, use, goodwill, or other intangible losses, resulting from (i) your access to or use of or inability to access or use the Service; (ii) any conduct or content of any third party on the Service; (iii) any content obtained from the Service; and (iv) unauthorized access, use or alteration of your transmissions or content, whether based on warranty, contract, tort (including negligence) or any other legal theory, whether or not we have been informed of the possibility of such damage, and even if a remedy set forth herein is found to have failed of its essential purpose.

**Disclaimer**

Your use of the Service is at your sole risk. The Service is provided on an "AS IS" and "AS AVAILABLE" basis. The Service is provided without warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, non-infringement or course of performance. Women Also Know Stuff, its subsidiaries, affiliates, and its licensors do not warrant that a) the Service will function uninterrupted, secure or available at any particular time or location; b) any errors or defects will be corrected; c) the Service is free of viruses or other harmful components; or d) the results of using the Service will meet your requirements.

**Exclusions**

Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of certain warranties or the exclusion or limitation of liability for consequential or incidental damages, so the limitations above may not apply to you.

**Governing Law**

These Terms shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of the state of Arizona and the United States, without regard to its conflict of law provisions. Our failure to enforce any right or provision of these Terms will not be considered a waiver of those rights. If any provision of these Terms is held to be invalid or unenforceable by a court, the remaining provisions of these Terms will remain in effect. These Terms constitute the entire agreement between us regarding our Service, and supersede and replace any prior agreements we might have had between us regarding the Service.

**Changes**

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a revision is material we will provide at least 30 days notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole discretion. By continuing to access or use our Service after any revisions become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised terms. If you do not agree to the new terms, you are no longer authorized to use the Service.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us at .

Close

[© 2024 - WomenAlsoKnowStuff](https://womenalsoknowstuff.com/) Privacy Notice Terms [Branding By Jasmine Osorio](https://www.linkedin.com/in/jasmine-osorio-283824164) [Site By AcademyBit](https://academybit.com/)
